var questions = [
    {
        "title": "Dictionary",
        "question": "Given a dictionary with the property <code>property1</code> and value <code>value1</code>",
        "subText": "Add an additional property <code>property2</code> and value <code>value2</code>.",
        "stage": {"property1": "value1"},
        "answer": {"property1": "value1", "property2": "value2"}
    },
    {
        "title": "Dictionary",
        "question": "Given a dictionary with the property <code>name</code> and value <code>apple</code>. Add additional properties to the dictionary.",
        "subText": "<table align='center'>  <tr>  <th>Key/Property</th>    <th>Value</th>  </tr>  <tr>    <td>name</td>    <td>apple</td>  </tr> <tr>    <td>color</td>    <td>red</td>  </tr>  <tr>    <td>weight</td>    <td>90g</td>  </tr>  </table>",
        "stage": {"name": "apple"},
        "answer": {"name": "apple", "color": "red" , "weight": "90g"}
    },
    {
        "title": "Dictionary in Dictionary",
        "question": "A dictionary <code>employee</code> is given. Add the remaining properties to it using information from the table below.",
        "subText": "<table align='center'>  <tr>  <th>Key/Property</th>    <th>Value</th>  </tr>  <tr>    <td>name</td>    <td>john</td>  </tr> <tr>    <td>gender</td>    <td>male</td>  </tr>  <tr>    <td>age</td>    <td>24</td>  </tr>  </table>",
        "stage": {"employee":{"name":"john"}},
        "answer": {"employee":{"name":"john","gender":"male","age":24}}
    },
    {
        "title": "Dictionary in Dictionary in Dictionary",
        "question": "Now try adding the address information. Note the address is a dictionary",
        "subText": "<table align='center'>  <tr>  <th>Key/Property</th>    <th>Value</th>  </tr>  <tr>    <td>name</td>    <td>john</td>  </tr> <tr>    <td>gender</td>    <td>male</td>  </tr>  <tr>    <td>age</td>    <td>24</td>  </tr> <tr>    <td> address </td>    <td> <table align='center'>  <tr>  <th>Key/Property</th>    <th>Value</th>  </tr>  <tr>    <td>city</td>    <td>edison</td>  </tr> <tr>    <td>state</td>    <td>new jersey</td>  </tr>  <tr>    <td>country</td>    <td>united states</td>  </tr>  </table> </td>  </tr>  </table>",
        "stage": {"employee":{"name":"john","gender":"male","age":24}},
        "answer": {"employee":{"name":"john","gender":"male","age":24,"address":{"city":"edison","state":"new jersey","country":"united states"}}}
    },
    {
        "question": "Given an array of apples. Add a new apple to the list to make it a total of 4.",
        "title": "List/Array",
        "stage": ["apple", "apple", "apple"],
        "answer": ["apple", "apple", "apple", "apple"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Add two more to make it 6.",
        "title": "List/Array",
        "stage": ["apple", "apple", "apple", "apple"],
        "answer": ["apple", "apple", "apple", "apple", "apple", "apple"]
    },
    {
        "question": "Add two 'mango'es to the list.",
        "title": "List/Array",
        "stage": ["apple", "apple", "apple", "apple", "apple"],
        "answer": ["apple", "apple", "apple", "apple", "apple", "mango", "mango"]
    },
    {
        "title": "List of Dictionaries",
        "question": "We would like to add additional details for each item, such as color, weight etc. We have updated the first one for you. Similarly modify the remaining items to match the below data.",
        "subText": "<table align='center'>  <tr>    <th>Fruit</th>    <th>Color</th>    <th>Weight</th>  </tr>  <tr>    <td>apple</td>    <td>red</td>    <td>100g</td>  </tr>  <tr>    <td>apple</td>    <td>red</td>    <td>90g</td>  </tr>  <tr>    <td>mango</td>    <td>yellow</td>    <td>150g</td>  </tr></table>",
        "stage": [{"name":"apple","color":"red","weight":"100g"},"apple","mango"],
        "answer": [{"name":"apple","color":"red","weight":"100g"},{"name":"apple","color":"red","weight":"90g"},{"name":"mango","color":"yellow","weight":"150g"}]
    },
    {
        "title": "List of Dictionary",
        "question": "We would like to record information about multiple employees. Convert the dictionary <code>employee</code> to an array <code>employees</code>.",
        "subText": "",
        "stage": {"employees":{"name":"john","gender":"male","age":24}},
        "answer": {"employees":[{"name":"john","gender":"male","age":24}]}
    },
    {
        "title": "List of Dictionary",
        "question": "Add an additional employee to the list using the below information.",
        "subText": "<table align='center'>  <tr>  <th>Key/Property</th>    <th>Value</th>  </tr>  <tr>    <td>name</td>    <td>sarah</td>  </tr> <tr>    <td>gender</td>    <td>female</td>  </tr>  <tr>    <td>age</td>    <td>28</td>  </tr> </table>",
        "stage": {"employees":[{"name":"john","gender":"male","age":24}]},
        "answer": {"employees":[{"name":"john","gender":"male","age":24},{"name":"sarah","gender":"female","age":28}]}
    },
    {
        "title": "List of Dictionary in Dictionary",
        "question": "Now try adding the pay information. Remember while <code>address</code> is a dictionary, <code>payslips</code> is an array of <code>month</code> and <code>amount</code>",
        "subText": "<table align='center'>  <tr>  <th>Key/Property</th>    <th>Value</th>  </tr>  <tr>    <td>name</td>    <td>john</td>  </tr> <tr>    <td>gender</td>    <td>male</td>  </tr>  <tr>    <td>age</td>    <td>24</td>  </tr> <tr>    <td>address</td>    <td> ... </td>  </tr> <tr>    <td> payslips </td>    <td> <table align='center'>  <tr> <th>#</th> <th>month</th>    <th>amount</th>  </tr>  <tr>    <td>1</td>  <td>june</td>  <td>1400</td>  </tr> <tr>    <td>2</td>  <td>july</td>  <td>2400</td>  </tr> <tr>    <td>3</td>  <td>august</td>  <td>3400</td>  </tr>  </table> </td>  </tr>  </table>",
        "stage": {"employee":{"name":"john","gender":"male","age":24,"address":{"city":"edison","state":"new jersey","country":"united states"}}},
        "answer": {"employee":{"name":"john","gender":"male","age":24,"address":{"city":"edison","state":"new jersey","country":"united states"},"payslips":[{"month":"june","amount":1400},{"month":"july","amount":2400},{"month":"august","amount":3400}]}}
    },
    {
        "title": "CONGRATULATIONS!!!",
        "question": "You have successfully completed the quiz!",
        "subText": "",
        "stage": {"employee":{"name":"john","gender":"male","age":24,"address":{"city":"edison","state":"new jersey","country":"united states"},"payslips":[{"month":"june","amount":1400},{"month":"july","amount":2400},{"month":"august","amount":3400}]}},
        "answer": {"employee":"sdfsdfsd"}
    }
]
